剧情回顾......
Previously on Lost...
你想让我救你的命?
You want me to save your life?
我想让你自己想救我的命
I want you to want to save my life.
我刚在 Ben 的肾脏旁边切了个小口
Just made a small incision in Ben's kidney sac.
如果我一小时内不把他缝上 他就会死
Now if I don't stitch that back up in the next hour, he's dead.
我希望你能进去
I would like for you to go back in there,
完成他的手术
put Ben under and finish the surgery.
我为什么要这样做?
And why would I want to do that?
因为我能帮你的朋友逃跑
Because I'm going to go help your friends escape.
- 不!  - Danny!
- N0!  - Danny!
Show me the way to go home
I'm tired,and I wanna go to bed
had a little drink about an hour ago
and it went straight to my head
别唱了!
Stop!
怎么 你想驾驶吗?
What, you wanna turn steering?
我们必须回去
We have to go back.
你到底在说什么?
What the hell are you talking about?
我们要回去 Sawyer
Turn the boat around, Sawyer,I mean it.
你疯了吗? 我们刚逃走
Have you lost your mind? We just got away.
照我说的做
Just do it.
- 请你给我一个理由  - 我们不能把 Jack 留在那里
- You give me one good reason to turn...  - Because we can't leave Jack behind.
是的 我们能 小妞...
Yes, we can, Freckles...
因为是他让我们这样做的
'cause that's what he asked us to do.
你想想  如果我们回去
I mean, think about it? We go back there,
被那个白痴猎人Ben抓到 他会怎么对待我们?
what do you think captain bunnykiller's gonna do if he catches us?
他会杀了你们的
He'll kill you.
上帝爱你像爱 Jacob 一样
God loves you as he loved Jacob.
谢谢你的建议
Thanks for the input.
抱歉 小妞...
Sorry, kiddo...
Jack 只能靠自己了
Jack's on his own.
是时候了
Time to get up.
我们要把你转走
We're moving you.
- 去哪里?   - 另外一个地方 Jack
- Moving me where?   - Someplace else, Jack.
为什么?
Why?
- 就这样了 是吗?  - "这样"?
- So this is it, huh?  -"It"?
你刚帮我救了他的命
You just helped me save his life.
你要杀我的话就说的直接点
If you're gonna kill me,pls,at least show me the respect of not calling it "moving."
我们为什么要杀你?
Now why would we kill you?
因为我已经没有利用价值了
Because you're done with me.
你以为我们是什么人?
What kind of people do you think we are?
我不知道 Tom
I don't know, Tom.
那种
The kind of people that would
劫持孕妇...
take a pregnant woman...
把 Charlie 吊在树上...
would hang Charlie from a tree...
把我们的人拖进丛林...
would drag our people out of the jungle...
还绑架儿童
would kidnap children?
我就是这么想的
That's the kind of people I think you are.
你看见你住的玻璃房了 Jack?
You see this glass house you're living in, Jack?
要不要去更舒服的地方?
How 'bout I get you some stones?
这很简单 你怎么说?
Let's do this the easy way. What do you say?
Jack 医生? Jack 医生?
Dr. Jack? Hey, Dr. Jack?
想要汽水吗 Jack医生?
Dr. Jack want soda?
你知道我不懂你说的话
You know I can't understand a word you're saying, right?
Jack 医生
Dr. Jack
别客气
You're welcome.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www.YYETS.com
■
翻译:  许愿
校对：许愿
■
双语字幕：    七色九天    chamber
后期：     梁良      字幕监制：  梁良
■
谢谢
Thank you.
十分感谢你
Thank you very much.
你不是这里的 是吗?
You're not from around here, are you?
对 我不是
No. No, I'm not.
我... 我叫 Jack
I'm... Jack.
Jack 我叫 Achara
Hi, Jack. I'm Achara.
Achara... Achara
Juliet 为我做的?
Juliet grilled these for me.
那个女人是谁?
Who's that woman?
她是司法长官
That'd be the sheriff.
- 你们有司法长官?   - 不完全是 Jack
- You have a sheriff?  - Not literally.
你们为什么要把 Juliet 转到我的房间?
Why are you moving Juliet into my room?
因为她有麻烦了 Jack
'Cause she's in trouble.
你别干傻事 老实待着
Now don't try anything stupid. You stay put in this cage, okay?
你们不是有监视器吗?
You say that like you're not watching me from that camera right there.
对了 Ben告诉我 你进过监控室
Oh, right. Ben told me you got into the surveillance room.
问你个问题
Let me ask you something.
你冒着生命危险
You risk your neck to cut them loose,
帮他们逃走...
and they run away and don't ever look back...
谢谢你给我的三明治
Thanks for the sandwich.
真没想到我又回来了
Never thought I'd be glad to get back to this rock again.
你在干吗?
What are you doing?
你说在干吗  我们要上岸啊!
What's it look like? I'm heading into shore.
如果我们沿着海岸继续划 可以划到我们的营地
If we just keep going, we can circle round.
我们可以告诉 Locke 和 Sayid 发生了什么
Sooner or later we'll get to camp and tell Locke and Sayid what happened.
我们会的是吗?
Oh, we will?
你有地图吗 麦哲伦小妞?
You got a map you ain't showing me, Magellan?
我们没有水没有食物
We got no food, no water,
在夜里我不能划这艘船
and I can't steer in the dark.
- 那么让我来  - 不行
- Then I'll steer.  - No.
我们上岸然后扎营
You'll come ashore, and we'll make camp.
你想贡献的话就把篝火点起来
You want to contribute?You can build a campfire while I carry the kid.
很高兴我们达成共识
Glad we agree.
- 你不饿吗?  - 不 James 我不饿
- Sure you ain't hungry?  - No, James, I ain't hungry.
你们不该吵架
You shouldn't fight.
你什么时候醒的?
When the hell did you wake up?
你们不该吵架 因为你们幸运的活了下来
You shouldn't fight because you're lucky to be alive.
我想他说到点子上了
Golly! I think he's got a point!
你们住在那座岛上吗?
That island we were on... Is that where your people live?
- 只是用来工作  - 什么工作?
- Just where we work.  - Work on what?
一些工程
Projects.
就像 "把孩子从木伐上偷走" 的工程?
Oh, sure, like the "steal the kid off the raft" project?
干的真是出色
That was a humdinger.
你们不是住在那座岛上的?
So you don't actually live on that island?
你住在这里...
Do you live here...
这座岛上吗?
on this island?
是的 女士
Yes, ma'am.
那你们为什么要抓那些人...
And what did you do with the people that you took...
和孩子们?
the kids?
我们要给他们更好的生活
We give them a better life.
相对什么?
Better than what?
相对你们的生活
Better than yours.
今晚不会有月亮了
There's not gonna be any moon tonight.
将是一片黑暗
It'll be dark.
晚上我和 Alex 通常躺在 我家的后院
Me and Alex used to lie in my backyard at night,
给星座取名字
make up names for the constellations.
你还看不见 但...
You can't see it yet,
那个是"ursa theodorus"...
but right there will be "Ursa Theodorus"...
泰迪熊
the teddy bear.
- 你还有后院?  - 是的
- You have backyards?  -Yeah.
那听起来真诱人
Well, ain't that quaint?
警报
Warning!
我以为你被关起来了
I thought you were locked up.
他们让我检查 Ben
They let me out to examine Ben.
他的器官活动很底 还有高烧
His vitals are low, and he has a fever.
这是我10分钟前拍的
I took this about ten minutes ago.
是他的缝针
It's of his stitches.
他们被感染了?
They're infected, aren't they?
是的
Yes.
你能来看看他吗?
Will you come look at them?
不行
No.
- Jack - 不行
- Jack.  -No.
你不必为他们... 或他这么做
I'm not asking you for them... or him.
就算是为了我
I'm asking you as a personal favor to me.
你想让我再帮他一次?
You... want me to help him again?
是的
Yes.
你确定吗 Juliet?
Are you sure about that, Juliet?
是的 我很确定
Yes... I'm sure.
这是因为他能让你回家吗?
And this is because he said that he would let you go home?
不是的
No.
不 我...
No, I...
因为我遇到麻烦了
It's because I'm in trouble.
- 麻烦? 为了...  - 我杀了个人
- Trouble? For...  - I just killed someone.
所以他们把我关起来了
That's why they put me in your room.
你杀了谁?
Who?
这很复杂
It's complicated.
让我直接和你说吧
Well, then, let me simplify it for you.
我不会帮他的...
I'm not gonna help him...
我也不会帮你
and I'm not gonna help you.
今日特别泰国菜 你尝尝
Special Thai dish for you. You try.
非常勇敢!
Very brave, very brave.
我哥哥喜欢你
My brother likes you.
我是一个受欢迎的人
Well, I'm a very likeable guy.
Jack...
问你个问题
tell me something.
说吧
Shoot.
为什么你不懂怎么放风筝?
Why is it you don't know how to fly a kite?
- 我从没学过  - 那真可惜
- Just never learned, I guess.  - That's very sad.
我爸工作很忙
Well, my dad worked a lot.
而且他也不是那种会喜欢放风筝的人
He wasn't exactly the kite-flying type, anyway.
- 我的意思是 我们  - Jack
- I mean, we never really...  -Jack
- 怎么了?  - 我对你父亲不感兴趣
- Yeah?  - I have no interest in your father.
好吧 我也厌倦了总是说起他
Well, that's a relief,because I'm pretty tired of talking about him.
有些事可以放在心里
Some things are personal.
你来 Phuket 是 "找回自我"?
So you're in Phuket to... "find yourself"?
- 为什么这么说?  - 你是个美国人
- Why would you say that?  - You're an American.
我有...
I have...
一个天赋
a gift.
那一定很值得期待
Must be one hell of a gift.
我在读你纹身上的字
I was just reading your tattoos.
"五" 和周围的星星都很漂亮
The "five" and the stars are very cute,
但那上面的中文字...
But the Chinese I find...
有点讽刺
a bit ironic.
- 什么讽刺?  - 它所表达的
- You find what ironic?  - What it says.
你知道它表示什么?
You do know what it says?
是的 我知道
Yeah, I know what it says.
你确定吗?
Are you sure?
中文是一种很复杂的语言
Chinese is a very complicated language.
我们往往会不能完全理解它的意思
It's fairly common for some things to get lost in translation.
- 我知道它表示什么  - 那好吧
- I know what it says.  - All right, then.
Jack...
我的名字叫 Isabel
My name is Isabel.
如果你跟我来
If you'll come with me,
我要问你几个问题
I'd like to talk to you and ask you a few questions.
你为什么不去看看你父亲 他会很高兴的
Why don't you check on your father, sweetheart? I know he'd appreciate it.
请坐 Jack
Please, have a seat, Jack.
我们今天聚在一起
As you may have gathered,
我们不住在这座小岛上
we don't live on this little island.
我们也不喜欢来这里
In fact, most of us don't really even like coming here.
我在调查一起暴力事件
There's been an incident that I'm investigating,
我要问你几个问题
and I need to ask you some questions,
希望你能解决这里的...
so I was hoping you may help me clear up
不安定因素
a few of the... inconsistencies.
如果我说错的话告诉我 Tom
Now correct me if I'm wrong, Tom,
你说在手术过程中
but you said, in the midst of a surgical procedure,
Jack 说 Juliet 让他杀死 Ben
Jack made several comments indicating that Juliet had asked him to kill Ben.
对
Yeah. That's right.
这是真的吗 Jack?
Is that true, Jack?
Juliet 有没有叫你杀了 Ben?
Did Juliet ask you to kill Ben?
问题很简单 Juliet 有没有叫你杀了 Ben?
The question's simple. Did Juliet ask you to kill Ben?
没有
No
没有 我撒了谎
No, I was lying.
我会尽全力救我的伙伴
I would've done anything to get my friends out,
所以我制造混乱
and turning you people against each other
让你们互相猜疑
was my best chance of creating chaos.
你为什么替她撒谎 Jack?
Why are you lying for her, Jack?
我想回我的牢房
I'd like to go back to my cage now.
谁在那儿?
Who's there?
你认为呢?
Who do you think?
几点了?
What time is it?
很晚了
It's late.
好咸啊
Salty.
我去大海游泳了
I went for a swim in the ocean.
洗刷一天的疲劳?
Washing the day off of you, huh?
你想问我什么 Jack?
Is there something you'd like to ask me, Jack?
什么都没有
No, not at all.
这样也好...
I mean...it might be nice...
已经一个月了
after a month of you coming and going whenever you want,
我还对你一无所知
to find out something about you.
这里发生的事你永远不会了解
There are things that happen here that you could never understand.
就像你的天赋?
Like your gift?
是的...
Yes...
就像我的天赋
like my gift.
你和我在一起快乐吗 Jack?
Are you having fun with me, Jack?
是的
Oh, yeah.
那就别问了  一起享受吧
Then stop ask questions.Let's have fun.
怎么?!
What?
嘿... Jack
Hey... Jack
我认识你吗?
Do I...do I know you?
815航班 你是...
815. You're...
- 你是那个乘务员  - Cindy
- you were the stewardess.  - Cindy.
你在这里干嘛? 我以为你被抓了
What are you doing here, with them?I thought you were taken.
- 被劫持了  - 他们不是...
- You were... You were captured. - They're not...
这没有那么简单
it's not that simple.
他们在这里干嘛? 你在这里干什么?!
What are they doing here right now? What are you doing here?!
我们是来参观的 Jack
We're here to watch, Jack.
参观什么?
Watch what?
怎么了 甜心?
What is it, sweetheart?
她想问 Ana Lucia 好吗
She... wants to know how Ana Lucia's doing.
你是认真的?
Are you serious?
如果你有什么要去参观的话 Cindy 那就去吧!
If you've got something to watch, Cindy, go watch it!
去呀!
Go!
- Sawyer  - 怎么了?
- Sawyer  - What?
Sawyer 快起来
Sawyer, wake up.
他跑了
He's gone.
Karl 跑了
Karl's gone.
去哪儿了?
Where?
我去吧
I got it.
不 让我和他谈谈
No, let me talk to him.
还是我去吧
No, I got it.
这是男生之间的事
Boys only.
你这是干嘛?
What the hell was that for?
你得振作起来
So you'd cowboy up.
在丛林里哭泣
Crying in the jungle.
本以为你们都很坚强
I thought you people were supposed to be tough.
我很坚强
I am tough.
是啊 Bobby
Sure you are, Bobby.
Bobby? "brady 帮"?
Bobby? "The Brady bunch"?
什么是"brady 帮"?
What the hell's "The Brady bunch"?
好吧 Karl...
Ok,anyway,look,Karl...
我和许多女孩交往过...
I've been with a lot of girls...
有些很值得...
some of them worth the trouble...
有些不是
some not.
直到现在...
Every now and again...
有那么一个人...
there's one...
你叫她"沉默星座"
one you name dumb stars with.
这个女孩 Sally Slingshot...
So this girl, Sally Slingshot...
- Alex  - 是啊
- Alex. - Yeah.
你爱她吗?
You love her?
胜过一切
More than anything.
那你就回去把她找回来
Then go back to wherever the hell your...yards are, and get her back.
如果我被抓了
If I get caught,
这次他们会杀了我的
they'll kill me this time.
那...
Well...
至少也值得
at least it'll be worth it.
我想问你些事
I wanna ask you something.
现在他们什么也看不到 你可以和我说真话
They're not watching anymore, so you can tell me the truth.
好吧
Ok.
Ben
你为什么要救他?
Why'd you save his life?
经历了这一切...
All this time...
他对你的人的所作所为...
After all he did to you and your people...
你应该恨他才对
you should hate him,
但你还是救了他的命
But you still fixed him up,
甚至在你朋友逃跑后 为什么?
even after your friends got away. Why?
你是他女儿
You're his daughter.
回答我的问题
Answer the question.
那你也要给我些答案
I'll answer your question if you answer one of mine.
Juliet 在哪里?
Where's Juliet?
他和他们在一起 他们正在读她的判决书
She's with the rest of them. They're gonna read her verdict.
她的判决书?
Her verdict?
我们都知道会发生什么
And we all know what it's gonna be.
自相惨杀从不被允许
We're pretty strict about killing one of our own.
一命抵一命
Eye for an eye.
她杀了谁?
Who? Who did she kill?
那个想要杀死你朋友的人
The man who was gonna murder your friends.
没想到你还挺关心她的
No wonder you're so worried about her.
如果不是为了你 她不会这么做的
If it wasn't for you, she never would have done it.
那是第三个问题了
That was three questions.
到你了 Jack
Your turn, Jack.
我救你父亲 因为我答应过他
I saved your father because I said I would.
他还掌管吗?
Is he still in charge?
什么?
What?
Ben 你父亲-- 他还在掌管吗?
Ben, your father...Is he still in charge?
Isabel 会听他的吗?
Will that woman Isabel do what he says?
是的
Yeah.
把我放出来
Get me out of this cage.
我不会这么做的
I wouldn't do that.
骑兵终于来了
The cavalry has arrived at last.
如果你们有个出色外科医生就好了
I'd be much more impressed with you people if you had a good surgeon.
我们曾经有的 Jack
We had an excellent surgeon, Jack.
他叫 Ethan
His name was Ethan.
已经大面积感染了 Ben
You have a very serious infection, Ben.
被感染的组织需要从新切开
That infected tissue needs to be re-incised, debrided,
你需要随时监控
and you need to be very closely monitored from here on out.
不然也许会造成神经受损 或者会有其它炎症
There might be nerve damage or any number of other complications.
你可能永远不能走路了
You might not walk again.
这话告诉我你另有所图
Your bedside manner leaves something to be desired.
谁让你和我困在一起了
Well, then, it's too bad you're stuck with me.
是吗?
Am I?
你需要一名医生 Ben
You need a doctor, Ben.
能和你待在一起
someone to stay with you
让你快点恢复
bring you back to good health.
又来了
And here we go again.
我已经答应你 让你离开这座岛了 Jack
I've already given you a ticket off this island.
这次你又要我做什么?
What's it gonna cost me this time?
现在你的人正在讨论
Right now your people are in a room
是否要处决 Juliet
deciding whether or not to execute Juliet.
你可以阻止他们
You're gonna stop it.
Juliet 不在乎你的 Jack
Juliet doesn't care about you, Jack.
不管她做了什么
Doesn't matter what she's done,
不论你怎么想...
No matter what you think...
她还是我们的人
she's one of us.
成交吗?
Do we have a deal or not?
Isabel 有对讲机吗?
Does Isabel have a walkie?
他们已经在开会了
They're already in the meeting.
那就拿纸过来写吧
Then get me something to write on.
你跟踪我
You following me.
这些都是什么?
What is all this?
这是我工作的地方
This is where I work,
你不该来这儿
and you shouldn't be here.
这是...
This is a...
纹身店 这就是你的秘密?
a tattoo parlor. This was your big secret?
信封... 你的天赋?
The envelopes... your gift?
我不是纹身艺术家
I am not a tattoo artist.
我能看出你是怎样一个人
I'm able to see who people are.
我的工作不是装饰...
My work is not decoration...
而是注释...
it is definition...
而这...
and this...
才是我的天赋
this is my gift.
那么...
So...
你能看穿人们
you see who people are.
是的... 然后帮他们做记号
Yes... and I mark them.
那告诉我我是怎么样一个人
So tell me who I am.
- 不行  - 为什么?
- No.  - Why not?
你是个外来者
You are an outsider.
那你就可以和我上床...
So you can sleep with me...
我不可以这么做
I'm not allowed.
你知道我是怎样一个人 是吗 Achara?
Do you see who I am, Achara?
是的
Yes.
那告诉我
Who am I?
你是一个领袖
You are a leader,
一个伟大的人
a great man.
但这...
But this...
会让你孤独...
this makes you lonely...
恐惧...
and frightened..
暴怒
and angry.
好
Good.
给我作标记吧
Now put it on me.
干吧!
Put it on me.
不 这...
No. This...
是在违背我们的人
this is against my people.
这会有报应的 Jack
There will be consequences, Jack.
当然会有
There always are.
等等 你不该在这里的
Wait. No, you shouldn't be here.
退后
Just stand back.
不要说话
Don't say anything.
Alex 你...
Alex, you...
Jack?
你把他带来干什么?!
What the hell did you bring him here for?!
放开他 Tom
Let him go, Tom.
怎么了 Alex?
What's going on, Alex?
这是 Ben 写的
This is from Ben.
Ben 减轻了 Juliet 的罪
Ben has commuted Juliet's sentence.
免除死刑
Execution is off the table.
他说规章不能改变
He says the rules don't apply.
但是 她必须被烙上印记
He has, however, ordered her to be marked.
你去哪儿?
Hey, where you going?
我认识你
Hey, I know you.
我是 Achara 的朋友 从...
I'm Achara's friend from...
我来过你的餐馆
Chet's,from the restaurant.
放开我 兄弟
Let go of me, man.
滚出我们的海滩!
You will get off our beach!
然后滚出这个国家!
You leave this country!
你明白吗?!
Do you understand me?
听说你只喜欢烤的
I heard you only liked them grilled.
我也想念这个牙签了
I missed the toothpicks, too.
- 让我看看  - Jack...
- Let me see.  - Jack...
他们给你做记号 让我看看
They marked you. Let me see it.
折一片芦荟给我...
Break a branch off that aloe plant over there...
- 没关系的 Jack   - 求你了
- It's ok, Jack.  - Please.
求你了
Please do it.
好了 转过身
All right, turn around.
为什么帮我?
Why did you help me?
他告诉你会让你回家
He told you he was gonna let you go home.
他也许诺我同样的事
He told me the same thing.
我们要保证他说到做到
We're gonna make sure he keeps his word.
我们怎么做?
And how are we going to do that?
一起面对
Together.
过几分钟他们都会来找你
They'll be coming for you in a few minutes... All of them.
你的朋友知道我们在哪儿
Your friends know where we are,
所以我们要回去我们住的地方
so we have to leave this island to go back to where we live.
去哪儿?
Go where?
Ben 叫它"家园"
Well, Ben calls it "home."
- Karl 在哪里?   - 我让他走了
- Where's Karl?  -I let him go.
- 什么?   - 我让他走了
- You what?  - I let him go.
他能带我们去他们住的地方
He could have led us back to where they live.
你以为我放了他 是因为我很敏感吗?
What, you think I cut him loose 'cause I'm so damn sensitive?
那孩子是靶子
The kid's a target.
Ben 不会放弃找到他 直到...
Ben ain't never gonna stop looking for him, so as long...
Ben 只想让他远离他女儿
All Ben wants is that kid as far from his daughter as possible.
我们回营地吧
Let's get back to camp.
你来不来啊?
Are you coming or not?
我是和你一起走 还是跟在你后面比较好?
Should I walk beside you or ten paces behind you?
难道你就不觉得很自私么?
You're so good at telling me what to do, I can't think for myself anymore.
别因为你自己有罪恶感 就把这些盖到我头上
Don't take it out on me 'cause you feel guilty.
- 我没感到罪恶  - 才怪!
- I don't feel guilty.  - The hell you don't!
我们必须留下Jack  我没有选择...
We had to leave Jack behind. I didn't have a choice...
我不是说这个
I'm not talking about leaving Jack behind.
我是说你我的事
I'm talking about you and me.
你这么做是因为 你知道我死定了...
I know you did it 'cause you thought I was a dead man...
不要因为医生还留在那里  而埋怨自己
so don't beat yourself up 'cause the doc's left behind.
我没有埋怨自己
I'm not beating myself up.
当然
'Course you're not.
现在我们可以走了吗?
So now that we got that out of the way, let's go.
"他与我们共同前进，但却不是我们的一员"
"He walks amongst us, but he is not one of us."
这就是你纹身的意义
Your tattoos...That's what they say.
这是他们说的
That's what they say.
但不是这个意思
It's not what they mean.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
双语版字幕由YYeTs春天花花英语教研组制作
仅供学习交流 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎有能力的爱好者加入我们字幕组 www.YYETS.com
■